Plus-Sized Elf
The Dark Elf and
the Beautiful Flower
Tomorrow's my day off...
Maybe I'll watch a movie.
Welcome.
Huh?
Kuroeda
"Kuroeda"?
Have I seen her here before...?
Popcorn
Soy Sauce
Butter Flavor
Eh, whatever.
Can't watch a movie without some popcorn!
Hm?
Wha-?!
Wh-what was that?
Excuse me, sir...
Is something the matter?
Eek!
A customer!
Here.
She was just picking it up for me...?
Welcome.
How professional.
I'll take the straight-cut fries, please.
Of course, ma'am.
Wait... Elfuda?
Oh, human! What a coincidence.
Eating fried food at this time of night...?
I-it's not what you think!
Th-the fact of the matter is
elves are required by law
to periodically consume French fries!
There is no such law.
Y-you! You're a dark elf!
Of all the places to run into an elf...
Yes, it's true! I am a dark elf!
Keep your distance, human...
Dark elves are evil creatures,
the very antithesis of my people!
They're vulgar and spiteful and
nefarious and never, ever on time!
Take that back, you little elven brat!
You elves are a bunch of arrogant,
condescending bumpkins
who hide inside your precious forests,
so I don't want to hear a peep out of you!
Excuse me?!
And you're the elf's friend?! Then-
No, we aren't friends per se...
[Insert exposition here]
Dine-in area is
currently closed
...And that's how I ended up taking her
on as one of my recurring clients.
Hm... Physical fitness, huh?
In that case, could I ask you to
help me out with my problem, too?
Problem?
It's probably easier to just show you.
When us dark elves use sorcery,
we adorn ourselves with special ornaments
and clothing to bolster our magic.
But every time I do...
...this happens!
I see...
My magic has suffered as a result.
Right now, I can only animate
a single golem!
And because of that, we're understaffed.
Honestly, it's exhausting...
Get back here!
There aren't any other employees...?
Which is why, if you're not a friend of
the elf, I request your assistance!
To get my magic back...
I need to tone my butt!
Uh... can we do this somewhere else?
I have to stay near the front end in case
a customer comes in and needs my help.
How professional.
So, how's it look?
You've got poor circulation...
And you've probably got some
muscle weakness, am I right?
Now, it can be a bit painful,
but if we massage this area here...
You liar! You ARE colluding
with the elf, aren't you?!
All I wanted was to tone my butt,
and you torture me instead?!
Pretending to cooperate
so I'd let my guard down...
You successfully put a dark elf to shame.
I applaud your little ruse!
Huh?! H-hold on...
My leg feels lighter...
How is this possible?
I can do your other leg, too.
Have a seat.
Travelling to this land in search of new magic
was a good idea after all!
What do you call this sorcery?
Regular old medicine...
Stop!
Will this help me lose weight?
It ought to reduce the swelling.
I recommend taking half-body baths
and massaging your legs.
Once a day, ideally.
Calf Raises
Stand with your legs shoulder width apart
and place your weight on the balls of your feet
Strength training would be
beneficial for you as well.
Use an elevated platform
for an effective alternative
Raise and lower your body in a controlled manner
while focusing on your calf muscles
That should prevent the swelling.
Front Lunges
Elongate your spine
but try not to bend forward
Building up muscle boosts
your metabolism and burns fat,
Front Lunges
This puts pressure on your knees,
so don't extend them past
the tips of your toes
As you exhale, slowly
and steadily sink your hips
so it can also help tone your glutes.
When doing squats, you'll want to
sink your hips while pushing your butt back.
This is pretty difficult...
The exercises I've shown you
don't require any weights,
so you can do them anywhere.
Which means I can do them at work.
Awesome!
Always the professional...
Hah, gotcha!
Pfft, talk about an unsightly view!
How appropriate for a dark elf!
An ass made of humongous, shiny dumplings!
Quit making fun of me!
At least my belly doesn't have
its own gravitational pull!
Well, at least my butt doesn't look like
two overinflated balloons!
It's better than looking like a snake
that swallowed a rat twice its size!
Hey, my stomach's pretty!
And my butt is cute!
L-ladies...?!
I think you're both attractive
exactly the way you are!
You'd be surprised how many guys like
a woman with some meat on her bones!
We're all shaped differently,
and it's just another part of
our unique charm, right?
Wait, why the judgmental faces?!
He actually likes humongous ass dumplings...?
He's into big, bloated snake bellies...?
Humans are a mystery...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The human was just trying to
end things on a positive note!
Well, I ate my fries, so I'm leaving.
Have a good one.
Come on! Don't ignore me!
For a while after that...
whenever I went to the corner store
where Kuroeda works...
Welcome.
Kishu Nanko Plum
(with honey)
Tirolo Chocolate
Have a good one.
...she'd throw in some freebies...
Where's my spoon...?
Baked custard
...and play a few harmless pranks
on me from time to time.
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf.
Massage Relaxation
Beauty - Health - Diet
I'm going on my break!
Okey-dokey!
A small flower shop opened up
in the neighborhood recently.
The owner introduced herself to me one day.
Since then, I've made a habit of
stopping by for a quick chat.
Hello there!
Another gorgeous day, isn't it?
Good afternoon, Kusahanada.
You're standing a little strange.
Are you alright?
Oh, I'm perfectly fine!
Huh? Something seems... off.
What a lovely day!
Yet another beautiful day!
Wonderful weather we're having!
Uh... is the flower on
your head getting bigger?
Is it that noticeable?
With all this sunny weather,
it's no wonder I'm getting heavier...
My shoulders are really sore, too...
Sunny weather makes her... heavier?
Maybe it's a sign that I ought to start
exercising more regularly?
Staying active isn't exactly my strong suit...
Do you have any tips?
Um... I'm running late today.
Can we talk some other time?
Please, don't trouble yourself.
I just thought I'd ask.
Massage Relaxation
...and that's how the conversation...
went.
Sounds like she might be an Alraune...
"Alraune"?
It's like a humanoid plant creature.
What?! She's a plant?!
Yes and no.
Alraune are sentient beings.
They've got emotions, too.
They absorb nutrients from the earth
and grow in the sunlight.
As a species, they're peaceful and friendly.
Ah, I knew it...
She is from another dimension.
The nice weather we've been having recently
would explain the overgrowth.
And the soil around here is full of fertilizer.
That makes sense...
Elfuda seems awfully knowledgeable...
But gaining weight 'cause of
some sunshine? Lame!
I do it the right way: with French fries!
Now that I've worked up a sweat,
how about a nice, crispy reward?
No French fries...
STARCH
Still, her anatomy must be
pretty different from ours...
That might complicate things...
What, you can't use your
encyclopedia brain like normal?
Well, my area of expertise is dieting...
and I think this falls under gardening.
That's not my wheelhouse.
You never know until you try!
I've been testing out all sorts of methods
in my quest to get fit!
Check it out!
I'm challenging myself to wear
a waist training corset right now!
Waist training...?
So instead of doing nothing and giving up,
be like me and give it
the old college try, human!
That's it!
Hey, boss!
Turns out I need to run a few errands,
so I'm heading out early!
Huh?!
But you promised we'd go out for drinks!
Sorry! I'll make it up to you next time!
Aww...!
Wh-what is it...?
A corrective back brace.
It promotes better posture and
reduces the burden on your muscles.
I think your poor posture is
the culprit behind your soreness.
When our posture is bad, it puts extra
strain on a singular part of the body,
resulting in stiffness and pain.
This back brace is designed to alleviate it.
But it's a little embarrassing...
I had you put it on over your clothes
so I could demonstrate the proper use.
Typically, it goes under your clothes,
so don't worry about the way it looks.
Oh, this is fantastic!
My body feels much lighter!
This is also for you.
My goodness, there's more?
As far as addressing the underlying issue...
I spent a lot of time thinking it over,
but this is all I came up with.
Try using it on days when
the sun is intense.
Your flower is very beautiful,
but be sure to regulate your daily
nutrient and sunlight intake, okay?
I will. Thank you.
Ah, that reminds me!
A token of my appreciation.
Evening Discount
SPA
Everyone says this sauna is top-notch!
Evening discount coupons?
I don't do so well in the heat...
Oh, but I heard the strangest rumor.
Apparently, there's an ogre
who appears in the sauna at night...